

### **ABOUT**

Hi, i'm Silvi Salputri, i'm a Informatics Engineering student at State Polytechnic of Batam.

Very passionate to learn about computer and technology and want to improve my skills on it. I understand HTML, CSS, PHP, MySQL, and i also interested in Network Administrator.

Experience during active the organizations, makes me have more soft skills, such as team work, discipline, problem solving, etc.

### **SKILLS**

Programming

Networking

Graphic Design

### **CONTACTS**









# SILVI SALPUTRI

**Informatics Engineering Student** 

## **EDUCATIONS**

2019 - PRESENT	State Polytechnic of Batam Informatics Engineering Major
2016 - 2019	Senior High School 3 Batam Natural Sciences Major
2013 - 2016	Junior High School 6 Batam

### **EXPERIENCES**

2007 - 2013

May - July

2021 - PRESENT	Dewan Legislatif Mahasiswa (DLM) In the Core Division as Secretary I in Dewan Legislatif Mahasiswa (DLM) Politeknik Negeri Batam.
2021 March	ARA CTF 2021 held by Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknologi Informasi (HMIT) ITS Capture The Flag participant in ARA CTF 2021.
2020 - 2021	Batam Linux User Group (BLUG)

**Elementary School 4 Lubuk Baja** 

	In the Core Division as <b>Secretary II</b> in UKM Batam Linux User Group
<b>2020</b> August	Arubalympics 2020  held by Aruba (a Hewlett-Packard Enterprise Company)  Scholarship recipients attend e-learning and e-competition based training with the theme "The Intelligence Campus Network 4.0". In this event, i got 3 Gold Medals and 1 Silver Medal.
2020	ID Camp 2020

	Learning Developer, so i get 3 certifications from Dicoding Academy.
<b>2019</b> July - August	Internship as Patient Administrator Internship as Patient Administrator at Ria Dental Care Botania

ID Camp participant and take Machine